PROFILE

A dedicated professional featuring technical and creative strengths with over 5 years of progressive experience in Program / Project Coordination, Website / Content / App Management and Development, Training and Technical Support. Proficient with using digital media, coding languages and CMS systems to create, edit, quality check and maintain websites and databases. Superior time management, organizational and analytical skills ensure the successful planning, administering and managing of projects. Self-motivated, able to initiate responsibilities, as well as a dedicated team player, committed to providing high-quality support and excellent problem-solving talents.

| TECHNICAE SINEES | | | |
|-------------------------------|-----------------------|---------------------------|-------------------------------------|
| | | | |
| Web Development: HTML5, CSS3, | DMS / OS: Windows, | Data Mining: BaseX, | Workspaces: Github, Cloud9, Heroku, |
| JavaScript, jQuery, Bootstrap | Xerox DocuShare, Mac | XPath, XQuery, Regex | Data Scientist Workbench, JS Fiddle |
| CMS: WordPress, Magento, | Database: Oracle, | Programming: C#, JS, | Digital Media: Adobe Photoshop, |
| dotCMS, Joomla, BigCommerce | SQL, MS Access, Visio | Python, ASP.NET, Velocity | SMART Technologies, MS PowerPoint |
| | | | |

TECHNICAL SKILLS

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Coding Instructor – Hatch Canada

2018 - present

- Lead programming lessons consisting of applications, games and exercises in p5.js, Processing and JavaScript
- Teach students from ages 7 to 17 in step by step lesson plans
- Answer questions, mark work and provide input on various coding projects completed by the students

Software Implementation Assistant / Web Developer – Canadian Memorial Chiropractic College

2016 - 2017 (3 contracts)

- Compiled, managed and deployed basic to advanced functions of the front end (user) and back end (client) of the DMS (Xerox DocuShare), including add-on features such as Lifecycle Manager and AutoStore
- Generated and implemented education and training modules of DMS for all staff and ensured departmental adoption
- Initiated technical support for company-wide assistance with DMS software set-up, program use and compliance
- Utilized dotCMS to create, edit and update content, styling, pages and templates, modifying to suit needs
- Programmed VTL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS files and widgets to deploy accurate and functioning content and web pages

Software

Website / Content Management: dotCMS Enterprise Cloud on AWS | HTML | CSS | Bootstrap | VTL - velocity

template language | JavaScript | Cyberduck FTP | dotCMS Widgets

Document Management System: Xerox DocuShare DMS

Web and Digital Specialist – Waterfront Regeneration Trust

2015 - 2016

(contract)

- Developed and expanded digital mapping and tourism web content, verifying accuracy and integrity of website
- Communicated project progress to partners through the creation of a project website and digital e-newsletters
- Created and programmed webpages and quality checked website integrity ensuring accuracy and accessibility
- Maintained and optimized the WRT's website, troubleshoot and fixed errors and researched and developed content
- Ensured project success and adherence to timelines by creating budgets, writing proposals and selecting contractors

CATJA MOSKAL

416.516.7267

catjamoskal@outlook.com Toronto, ON

Software

Website / Content Management: Joomla | Weebly | HTML | CSS | JavaScript | Joomla Plugins and Extensions

Digital Marketing: Constant Contact | Google Analytics | Google AdWords | Hootesuite

Project Management / Database: Google Docs | Google Sheets | MS Excel

Design / Presentation: Google Maps | MS PowerPoint | Pixlr | Canva | Adobe Acrobat | Adobe Photoshop

Online Digital Administrator - Hipstreet

2015

(contract)

- Managed website content, including developing, editing and publishing content, uploading accurate SKUs, ensuring information accuracy and increased brand awareness and driving sales
- Updated and generated web hyperlinks and widgets and performed quality assurance, keeping website current
- Produced and distributed email campaigns, including design, copywriting, graphics and building lists and split tests
- Improved performance by capturing and analyzing appropriate data/metrics, insights and best practices

Software

Website / Content Management: WordPress | BigCommerce | Magento | HTML | CSS

Digital Marketing: MailChimp | Sprout Social | Buffer | Feedly | Rafflecopter | Bitly | WordPress Blog

Project Management / Database: Asana Project Management | Google Docs - Sheets | MS Excel | MS Outlook

Design / Presentation: Adobe Photoshop | Adobe Illustrator | MS Powerpoint | SlideShare

Workshop Coordinator - Scientists in School

2009 - 2015

- Effectively planned, developed and presented successful workshops that led to multiple requests for repeat workshops
- Coordinated all workshop scheduling and delivery, maintained accurate records, managed the on-line database, keeping managers and staff informed and increased communications and efficiency
- Direct point of contact for clients, provided logistics and follow up and responded to all inquiries in a timely and efficient manner, resulting in a 98% client satisfaction rating
- · Prepared, maintained and updated materials, considering client feedback and keeping content relevant

EDUCATION

Web Applications Development Programming – Centennial College (TBC 2018)

Commercial Web Application Development - George Brown College (TBC 2018)

Advanced Web Art and Design, CSS and JavaScript Frameworks - OCAD University

Web Master Program – The YMC

Digital Marketing Management Certificate – University of Toronto

Project Management Certificate – University of Toronto

Honours Bachelor of Science (Hon. B.Sc.) – University of Toronto